Vanessa：AAAAAAAAAAHHH!!!!! KILL!!! KILL... DIE...!!
Vanessa：으아아아아! ! 죽죽죽죽......죽여버리겠어......! !
Vanessa：Everyone... must DIE!!!!
Vanessa：모두......두두두 죽어! !
PAFF：Oh no... It's absolutely horrifying.
PAFF：안 돼......수가 더 많아졌어요. 접근할 방법이 없어요!
Xenon：Be patient! We're working on it!
Xenon：조금만 참아! 우리도 노력 중이야!
NEKO：AAAHHH!!! All of you... just die already!
NEKO：으아아아! 이 망할 로봇 녀석들이!
NEKO：Give Cherry... Give everybody back!!
NEKO：Cherry 언니를... 모두를 돌려줘!!
ConneR：This truly... isn't easy to deal with...
ConneR：정말......상당히 곤란한 상황이로군...
ConneR：Miss Nora, how is outside looking?
ConneR：Nora 양, 바깥 상황은?
Nora：ROBO is looking pretty good.
Nora：ROBO 상태는 아직 괜찮습니다.
Nora：Sagar and Mr. Miller are keeping them at bay.
Nora：바깥엔 Sagar 씨와 Miller 씨가 막고 있어요.
Nora：Right now, there are no major issues!
Nora：잠시 동안은 괜찮을 겁니다!
Vanessa：Ugh... Urgh... Ughh...
Vanessa：으......으으......
PAFF：Her expression... it's changing!
PAFF：표정이 변했어!
Vanessa：NEKO i-i-i-is... w-w-w-worthless...
Vanessa：NEKO 도도도....아무짝짝짝짝에도  쓸모 없없는 사람....
NEKO：......!? What the...? She's talking nonsense!
NEKO：......! ? 뭐라구!? 갑자기 무슨 말이야!
Vanessa：I-I-I-I-I am unable to forgive myself,
Vanessa：나나나나는 아직 나를 용서할 수 없어.
Vanessa：b-b-but... c-c-can you forgive me?
Vanessa：하하하지만....너너너너는 나를 용서할 수 있을까?
Xenon：......! Sherry...
Xenon：......! Sherry......
ConneR：Again...? Don't be fooled, she wants to weaken our spirits!
ConneR：또.....？속아선 안 됩니다.
Vanessa：... I always wanted you to live in the world of our dreams...
Vanessa：......나는 네가 그런 세상에서 살아가길 바랬어...
Vanessa：Now, you'll have to create it on your own...
Vanessa：지금...네 스스로 만들어야만 해.....
Nora：Oh... Her memory is getting mixed up with the memories in the OS space.
Nora：큭......여러분! 녀석의 기억이 OS 공간의 기억들과 혼합되면서
Nora：She's getting weaker.
Nora：상당히 취약해졌어요!
Nora：But we must be quick.ROBO has almost reached max capacity...
Nora：그래도 빨리 서둘러야 합니다! ROBO도 더 이상은 한계입니다...
Vanessa：I... Ivy... *sob*... Save me...
Vanessa：I......Ivy......흐흑......구해줘......
Nora：No!!! I've got to disconnect you three,
Nora：안 돼! 지금 여러분 세 사람의 연결을 끊겠습니다!
Nora：ROBO is going to get fried!
Nora：더 이상은 ROBO가 타버릴 거예요!
PAFF：Okay! Get out of here! I'm heading in!
PAFF：괜찮아요! 여러분은 떠나세요! 전 계속 들어가겠어요!
Nora：Can't do it... eh? ROBO!?
Nora：방법이......응？ROBO! ?
Xenon：What happened!?
Xenon：무슨 일이지! ?
Nora：ROBO locked his system! I can't shut him off...!
Nora：ROBO가 자신의 시스템을 잠궈버렸어요! 제 권한이...!
ConneR：Was it to keep us connected longer...?
ConneR：우리들의 연결 시간을 연장시키려고 그런건가...?
ConneR：What a coincidence, it's not like we can just walk around as we please in here...
ConneR：마침 이곳도 마음 먹은대로 되는 상황이 아니라서......
Nora：ROBO! What are you doing!? Stop continuing to increase the power output!
Nora：ROBO! 뭐하는 짓이야!? 더 이상 출력을 높혀서는 안 돼!
Nora：You're going to...
Nora：그렇게 하면 넌...
Vanessa：I... Ivy... W-W-We... promised... *sob*...
Vanessa：I......Ivy......우우우리들......약속......흑흑......
Vanessa：Please... kill... kill me...
Vanessa：부탁해....빨리...날... 죽여줘...
PAFF：... Oh...
PAFF：......으윽......
Xenon：PAFF! Now!!!
Xenon：PAFF! 지금이다! !
NEKO：Wah! What happened!?
NEKO：우앗! 무슨 일이지!?
ConneR：The connection was cut. Which means...
ConneR：연결이 중단됐군요. 그렇다는 것은...
Nora：ROBO! ROBO!!...*sob*... AAAAAHH!!!
Nora：ROBO! ROBO! ! 안 돼에에에에! ! !
PAFF：Nora……
PAFF：Nora……
Nora：... Don't worry about me!
Nora：......이곳은 신경쓰지 말고! 어서 빨리 당신들이 해야 할 일을 하세요!!
Vanessa：You are... PAFF... right...?
Vanessa：......PAFF라고......했나......？
Vanessa：Please, hurry... kill me...
Vanessa：너희들에게 부탁할게... 빨리... 나를....죽여줘....
Vanessa：I don't want to suffer anymore...
Vanessa：그리고... 더 이상 인간들에게.... 고통을 주고 싶지 않아.....
Vanessa：I only want to be... with Ivy...
Vanessa：난 그저...  Ivy 와 함께......
PAFF：Oh......
PAFF：......
Vanessa：There's no time... Kill me...
Vanessa：시간이 없어.....날 죽여줘......
Nora：What are you doing!? Hurry!
Nora：뭣들 하고 계세요! ? 빨리 서둘러요!
PAFF：...... But, but...
PAFF：......하, 하지만....
Vanessa：The time... has come.
Vanessa：시간이......다 됐다.
PAFF：... Everyone, I'm sorry...
PAFF：......여러분.... 미안해요...